Guide to the Miles & Edwards and Charles Hindley & Sons Correspondence
Yale Center for British Art, Rare Books and Manuscripts
- Letter: London., 1874 March 6; Midleton, Augusta Mary Brodrick, Viscountess of, d. 1903 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  Requesting the company to arrange two places [in the shop?] from which to view a royal procession.
- Letter., [Unidentified year] June 25; Milbanke, Augusta, Lady. Thorp Persow (Box 2, Folder 118)
  Ordering a piece of "furniture print" fabric, a piece of blue dining calico, and a table cover with striped colors and a fringe.
- Letter., 1858 November 11; Montague, Jane Margaret, Lady (Box 2, Folder 119)
  Giving notice that she received barely 7 yards out of the 10 yards of fabric she had ordered.
- Letter., 1873 June 27; Monteagle of Brandon, Thomas Edmund Spring-Rice, Baron, 1849-1926 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  Regarding a disputed bill.
- Letter: East Bergholt, Suffolk., 1838 May 14; Morton, Frances Theodora Douglas, Countess of, d. 1879 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  Acknowledging receipt of a bed and furniture, returning several chintz patterns, requesting new patterns of green and white striped or figured chintz for armchair covers.
- Letter: London (?)., 1852 December 28; Munro, Jane, Lady, d. 1850 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  Regarding delivery of furniture and curtains.
- Letter: Buntingford., 1844 May 18; Murray, Susan Catherine Sanders, Lady, d. 1860 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  Ordering two chairs and two table covers.
- Letter., 1844 July 20; Normanby, Maria Phipps, Marchioness of, 1798-1882 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Letter., 1841 April 19; Northbrook, Arabella Georgina Baring, Baroness, 1809-1884 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  Regarding delivery of fringe, lining, and sewing silk.
- Letter., [Unidentified year] March 6; Parker, Lady Perthshire (Box 2, Folder 126)
  Ordering 100 yards of chintz with a pale buff background, and lining.
- Letter: Cambridge., Undated; Philpott, Henry, 1807-1892 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  Inquiring about a set of trays to fit inside a wardrobe he had ordered; complaining about the quality of a mirror he received.
- Letter: Wakefield., [After 1857] April 25; Pilkington, Isabella Elizabeth Georgiana, Lady (Box 2, Folder 128)
  Ordering 9.75 yards of white and red striped fabric, 9.75 yards of brown and red fabric, and inquiring whether they are also available in another width.
- Letter., 1845 January 23; Ripon, Sarah Louisa Albina Robinson, Countess of, 1793-1867 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  Ordering 60 yards of fabric and thread to match.
- Letter: Brighton., 1841 July 10; Rivers of Sudeley Castle, George Pitt-Rivers, Baron (Box 2, Folder 130)
  Regarding the status of an order for rods and curtains.
- Letter: Claybury, Wales., 1841 August; Riversdale, Charlotte Theodosia, Lady, d. 1853 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  Ordering one piece of "blue trellis furniture calico", and one piece of "speckled dining."
- Letter: London., 1852 April 27; Romilly, Georgiana Elisabeth, Lady, d. 1867 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  Requesting three painted towel horses for a nursery to be sent with her dining room table.
- Letter., 1852 June 22; Rosebery, Archibald John Primrose, Earl of, 1783-1854 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  Regarding a table cover.
- Letter: London (?)., 1848 July 26; Salis, Cecilia Henrietta Margaret Bourgeois, Countess (Box 2, Folder 134)
  Requesting a meeting to settle her bills.
- Letter: Kirkcudbright, Scotland., 1838 November 8; Selkirk, Joan Douglas, Countess of, d. 1871 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  Regarding fabric patterns and the matching of a red color.
- Letter: Kirkcudbright, Scotland., 1843 October; Selkirk, Joan Douglas, Countess of, d. 1871 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  Requesting patterns of green [illegible] and cotton velvets, and regarding a previous order of curtains and fringe.
- Letter., 1852; Shaftesbury, Emily Ashley-Cooper, Countess of, d. 1872 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  Inquiring about a set of white net curtains.
- Letter: Albany., 1852 December 6; Sidmouth, Mary Addington, Viscountess of, 1794-1894 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  Declining to purchase a carpet, but ordering a 7-foot rug in its place.
- Letter: London., 1871 October 30; Somers, Caroline Harriet Cocks, Countess of, d. 1873 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  Ordering 3 yards of crimson Brussels carpet, and 3 yards of [Coctonne?].
- Letter: Harleston, Northhampton., 1873 August 11; Southampton, Ismania Catherine Fitzroy, Lady, d. 1918 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  Ordering 3 yards of cord.
- Letter., 1843 March; Stewart, Caroline, Lady, d. 1850 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  Requesting someone to visit her with a samples of chintzes for a sofa and armchairs.
- Letter: Stoneleigh Abbey, Kenilworth., 1871 May 11; Stoneleigh, Caroline Amelia Leigh, Lady, circa 1828-1906 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  Regarding an order of white lining calico, and pink lining.
- Letter: Isle of Wight., 1841 January 24; Swinburne, Jane Henrietta, Lady, 1809-1896 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  Reporting that the twill she received was thicker than what she ordered; requesting that they either replace it or send some small-patterned chintzes and lining fabric samples in its place.
- Letter: Broughton Hall., 1849 July 29; Tempest, Charles Robert, Sir, 1794-1865 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Letter., 1841 June 28; Whichcote, Marianne, Lady, d. 1849 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Letter., 1843 November 20; Windsor, Harriet Clive Windsor, Baroness, 1797-1869 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  Ordering 15 yards of moreen and 70 yards of matching binding, to cover some seats.
- Letter: Ashburton House., [1870?] July 6; Winnington, Anna Helena, Lady, circa 1817-1883 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  Ordering 80 yards of fabric.